[{"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [1, 4, 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [1, 3, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [1, 2, 3], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 1, 2], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-松鼠.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-松鼠R.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 3, 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-松鼠.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-松鼠R.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 2, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-松鼠.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-松鼠R.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蝴蝶.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Front/蝴蝶_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [1, 2, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 3, 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-松鼠.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-松鼠R.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 1, 3], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [1, 2, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小猪.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/猪_R1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-松鼠.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-松鼠R.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜻蜓.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/蜻蜓_F1.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 3, 5], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}, {"body": [{"title": "动物分类选择", "stem": "选一选，给会飞的动物涂上颜色。", "content": [{"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-小鸟.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-带色-小鸟.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-小狗.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Right/小狗_R1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-奶牛.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/哺乳动物/哺乳类动物_1组/Left/牛_L1.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-蜜蜂.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/1-动物基础分类/节肢动物/Left/蜜蜂_L2.svg"}, {"type": "fly", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/会飞的-线描-鹦鹉.svg", "src2": "v2/通用/动物/2-特殊分类-能飞的/鹦鹉_带棍F1.svg"}, {"type": "run", "src1": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-线描-山羊.svg", "src2": "v2/组件/分类与整理/1-4-1-02/地上跑的-带色-山羊.svg"}], "selectType": "fly", "type": "au-animal-color"}], "answers": [0, 3, 4], "knowledges": ["分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "1", "number": "1-4-1-02"}]